GENIE, MAKE A WISH
You spent the night out? Where did you go?
I clearly told you
that I'd just change my clothes, and…
What's wrong? What happened?
A Mongolian boy paid me a visit.
He gave me back my memories.
I caused you…
My arrogance made you…
I found out about everything.
That doesn't matter anymore.
That's just the past.
We're here now.
You said you can't resurrect the dead
or take us to the future.
But actually, it was the future just now.
Just now and just now. And just now again.
Let's go together.
Not to the past that's set,
but to the future we can change.
Even if we don't know how it will end.
All right.
Let's do that.
CHOI DA-JIN
ENTER PASSWORD
INCORRECT PASSWORD
So you don't remember the password at all?
Stop joking around.
I'm not joking. It's killing me too.
I honestly have no clue.
Can't you use
two-step verification to reset it?
I guess I didn't register my number.
I'm not getting the codes.
Da-jin.
Come on, stop messing with me, seriously!
This is driving me insane too!
It's like I've lost my memory!
Like you've lost your memory?
Memory?
So she doesn't remember a thing
about the wishes. Every single detail.
That's why…
she's forgotten the password?
What do we do about our videos?
Yeong-hyeon, I'm sorry.
Why did I do that?
Why on earth did I change the password?
Our wedding anniversary, your birthday,
the day I first met you,
the day you proposed… It's none of those.
So, your passwords
were all things like that?
I must be out of my mind.
How could I forget this?
INCORRECT PASSWORD
Da-jin.
I'll make sure
your dad
gets better.
What? What are you talking about?
Where are you going?
Ka-young.
What's with you? What is all this?
Who is that bastard?
That jerk named you when he surrendered--
It's all right. It's all okay.
It will all be all right.
For now, let's go. You too, Min-ji.
You both need to remain in hiding
from now on. I know a secure place.
Sure. Lunatics like him
don't deserve the time of day.
Running away is the right thing to do.
Let's finish talking when we get there.
Where is it? Is it far?
About Heung-rye's funeral…
I'll make a generous gift.
For now, take this and get some sleep.
I have something I need to do.
It must be done for everything to be okay.
So even if it gets stifling,
make sure you stay here, Grandma. Okay?
All right.
Be careful, okay?
You'll go with her, won't you?
Yes. Don't worry, Oh Pan-geum.
I'll stay by her side.
The thing I said I'd tell you later--
Forget it. You don't need to tell me.
I already know it's Grandma.
I'll consider this a housewarming
and get comfy.
I see you've made yourself at home.
Your dinner delivery has arrived.
If you need anything, tell him.
Sade, protect them with your life.
Yes, Master. Leave it to me.
Want jjajang or jjamppong?
A genie, a beast, and a lamp
that's like a luxury Banpo Xi apartment.
Despite all of this magic,
I must make it clear where I stand.
My vote is still on evolution.
Right, about that.
That deserves its own conversation.
Why don't you take something
and sleep it off?
I could just…
- Kim Ha-neul, did you find your toy?
- Yes.
See? Daddy told you it would turn up.
But you had to cry and make a fuss.
Where was it? We couldn't find it
when we were looking for it.
Ppoppi told me where it was.
How could Ppoppi tell you?
Mommy told you he went to America.
It's true.
Ppoppi told me when he came last time.
He whispered it to me.
What's wrong?
I, a former member
of the Reconnaissance Unit,
inherited an enormous sum of money
from an anonymous person.
But I don't remember anything.
In situations like these, there are
three options. The first option is to…
Report it.
The second is…
NEAT STACK SAFE
Stash it.
The third and final option is…
So you've been abandoned too.
Do you want to come with me?
My house is full of your friends.
Before any of that,
what should we call you?
Ppoppi.
Yes, Ppoppi sounds good.
Chauffeur Choi?
Let's get going, shall we?
I chose the third option.
It's strange, and I miss it.
I feel like I will forever be waiting.
Even the anonymous have names.
I, now an abandoned dog detective,
am on my way to find those of you
who have abandoned your pet dogs.
Have you still not made up your mind?
That won't do, will it?
I'm not sure what you're playing at
by holding out like this,
but all you need to do
is put the world to sleep immediately.
Obey Father's orders
so that he can bind Iblis.
The door is open.
You total psycho.
What the hell are you doing?
I'll give you all of this money.
Sell me your final wish.
If you don't sell it, I'll burn it all.
I'm sure you're aware
that I will actually set it on fire.
Whatever wish you make,
I will simply wish to undo it.
So just sell it to me.
I'm asking you to please…
choose the money, Gu Bo-gyeong.
Why would I trust you?
We don't need to trust each other.
We need rules.
I follow rules, no matter what.
You hand over your wish,
and I hand you this money.
That would be it.
This would be our rule.
What do I need to wish for?
I'll make my final wish.
Go and tell Ki Ka-young
that I made the wish exactly as she asked.
In your past life, you sold hundreds
of lives to buy your way into heaven.
Now, in this life, you're still
causing trouble for others, Ms. Ki.
A bit rich coming from you.
You scared an eight-year-old
into using her final wish
to confine Iblis.
And you're still doing that
in this life. Get lost.
I simply stated the facts.
Not all facts tell the truth.
It's a pity,
but no matter what you do,
I will slit Iblis's throat.
I followed his orders
and bowed before humans.
Iblis, however,
rebelled against his every word.
Not once
has he obeyed his orders willingly.
The only reason
he continues to forgive Shaytan
is so I may slit his throat.
That means that my slitting Iblis's throat
is something he will truly rejoice in.
What's with the engineering student logic?
My arm hurts.
See here, Mr. Angel.
That thing you're doing right now?
It's called envy. An inferiority complex.
It is greater than that.
- My will aligns with his--
- Don't hide behind him!
You will never slit Iblis's throat.
Do you know why?
Because I will make
an incredibly selfish final wish.
I was…
always…
born evil.
JOY
DESPAIR
LONGING
WAITING
MIN-JI'S EMOTIONS ARE SO EASY
RULE: NEVER SNEER AT PEOPLE LIKE THIS
I knew you'd take a peek
eventually, you Satan.
Turn it off when you're done.
Electricity is not free.
Did you meet Gu Bo-gyeong?
She still seems to remember.
Did she do it?
Did she make her final wish?
She did. As did Ko Yeong-hyeon.
Human kindness
is very surprising.
They weren't corrupt.
Really?
Hey, wake up.
Ko Yeong-hyeon, wake up, will you?
How did you know? Tell me how.
Hey, what's wrong? Why are you crying?
What did I know?
Before you left,
you said you'd make Dad better.
I just heard that my dad's
cancer cells have disappeared.
No one knows why.
The doctors say it's a miracle!
- Wait, really?
- Yes!
Hey, that's amazing news!
Hold up.
Did I really say
something like that? When?
Thank you, Yeong-hyeon.
It's as if your words made him better.
Like some kind of magic.
It's okay. Hey, your phone.
Right.
Hi, Dad.
I was just telling him.
What?
Slow down. What's blowing up your phone?
Two-step verification codes
for a YouTube account? They went to you?
What codes…
Dad, you'll get another code now.
Read it out to me.
Yeong-hyeon, we can restore
all of our videos.
We have almost over 600,000 views now!
- Yes.
- Six hundred… thousand?
Did you just say
our video has over 600,000 views?
- Hey!
- What?
- Did you flash your chest?
You scumbag. Come here, you.
- Hey, I'm sorry!
- That's your first thought?
So does that mean I won't be dying
because of our bet?
I say we should count
Gu Bo-gyeong's final wish as 0.5,
and I'll try to argue the point
that it's 2.5 to 2.5.
I'm heading off now.
Make sure you come to save me, Master.
Right now?
Already?
Since the dawn of time,
the first to strike has won.
Don't worry.
I've never lost to anyone except you…
Knowing that one of them
must be destroyed,
I see Iblis has come to entertain
the impossible hope that both might live.
As it stands now,
both Iblis and Ms. Ki Ka-young
will try to save each other.
That certainly seems the case
for Ki Ka-young.
Then I won't be able to finish this war.
Did you say war?
Please, child. Stop.
I will put the world to sleep
and bind Iblis.
The day has finally come.
It's today?
Is today finally the day, Father?
That's why I will do the binding.
I no longer heal when cut by this thread.
I can simply not fall asleep.
Khalid!
All right. Now sing!
Iblis has come willingly.
Father, sing.
I said sing!
When that day comes,
there is something you must do.
That's all you need to do.
Am I understood?
We meet at last.
I have waited 1,000 years for you.
So you really had to go this far.
I received something invaluable today.
Thank you, Father.
Now, my son, will you grant me freedom?
Yes, that's right.
But
I'd rather take that freedom for myself.
Shadi!
Don't forget my last request, Iblis.
This was, I'm afraid,
the best I could do, my brother.
You do not possess the soul of a human
nor the generosity of a spirit.
You will…
die by my hands.
Are you angry?
Aren't you being too harsh
on an orphan who can't hear?
What about that bitch? Do you have her?
It's time for you to make your final wish.
Where is the lamp?
Refusing will only harm
the ones you care about.
Your grandma, your friend,
your village neighbors.
Will you wish to transfer ownership
of the lamp to me, friend?
So this is a zero-sum game.
Fine.
Enough with the faux friendship.
Just knock yourself the fuck out.
In quotes.
What are you saying?
Where the hell is the lamp?
What the hell? Where did she go?
That crazy bitch
just wasted her final wish like this?
Find her at once!
Yes.
What do I need to wish for?
Whatever the day or the moment,
when Ki Ka-young says,
"Just knock yourself the fuck out,"
take Ki Ka-young to Iblis's side.
That's what you'll wish for.
Did you get that?
What do you take me for?
Damn it. They really tied you up good.
This is the extent of my plans.
What do we do now?
This is where my plans start.
For starters, we have thread.
With that thread in hand,
I'll head to my brother's garden.
You two, follow me.
Everyone else, spread out!
Hurry and find her!
He's half-human, half-spirit.
That thread is fatal to him too.
Though I'm not sure I can carry it.
Carry it.
Don't worry about me. Just go.
Go get rid of the immortal one.
Oh my, I feel sick. I think we're being
taken somewhere else right now.
What could be happening?
I'll go and check things out.
Who are you? Another mythical beast?
Irem.
This is a gift from Ejllael.
A gift?
This must be it.
This is Iblis's lamp.
Irem, what did you just do?
I told you to do what's right by you.
I'm just following my master's orders.
This is what Ejllael ordered? Why exactly?
We do not question our masters' orders.
We simply obey.
Irem!
How come I can still see this?
It's meant to disappear
once you've made your three wishes.
She deceived me.
There's one wish left!
That bitch.
Go find her.
Find her, whatever it takes. Hurry!
Yes!
Stop right there!
I'll kill you all.
The day you find dead birds
on the roads for no reason,
that is the day.
Please come to save us.
You're not here to see me, are you?
I'm in the middle of something.
Ki Ka-young will soon be
making her final wish.
I thought I'd try
to buy some time until then.
If you strike that flower before then,
it would destroy my plans.
About your painting.
You asked why I took the angels' eyes.
They were full of desire.
And I see this is the desire I sensed.
For you, the 300-year war
isn't over.
Did you really believe that war was over?
Did that war bring an end to anything?
That is why
you shouldn't have removed that sword.
The very sword that annihilated us angels.
You should never
have met her again either.
Now you've recovered your memories,
you must know how things ended.
I hope Ki Ka-young's wish
will be righteous.
Then I will slit your throat
and put her back
to the way she always was.
She will forget you
and return to the hell she once lived in,
condemned as a psychopath.
Because that is the appropriate fate
for a human
who was loved by Satan.
In her previous life and now.
I also hope, more than anyone…
that her last wish will be righteous.
She may have been born evil,
but she lived a dull life
to avoid bad choices.
I hope the rest of her life is heaven.
Of course she would forget me
and go back to her normal life,
being condemned as a psychopath.
And her life may be dull,
but she would be a righteous human,
worthy of love, just as he intended.
I'm sure that's why we were reunited.
So that the end of this war…
may be Ki Ka-young's heaven.
So you, too, must bow.
Bow before her.
CONVENIENCE STORE CLERK
FORMER MARINE, CLASS 1185
STRAWBERRY FARMER
WELTERWEIGHT CHAMPION
CAFE OWNER, NEW CIVVIE
ALL FORMER MARINES
CHEONGPUNG MARINES
PARK CHANG-SIK
Operation Cave Cleaning.
From grit to grit.
If it won't do, make it do.
If it won't work, make it work.
All right, let's go!
Who are you? How did you get in here?
Are you another one of those things?
I'm sorry, I can't hear.
Your granddaughter's
waiting for you outside.
My Ka-young is here?
But who are you?
Where did you get it?
That thread.
Grandma, no matter what,
don't let go of my hand.
What the hell are you blabbering about?
Look at me.
I said look at me!
Your granddaughter made my father mad,
so I think it's time to drop some corpses.
Which order would be the most threatening?
I guess the friend first
and then blood relations, right?
Kill her first.
Who are you people?
What is all this?
Father!
It must be today.
Not next spring.
Grandma, try breaking the thread.
What the…
When the plum blossoms
next bloom in your garden…
Good heavens.
…you will die.
What is it?
Min-ji.
Make sure you tell my dear Ka-young
everything I tell you now.
Ka-young.
Raising you was such a blessing.
You got good grades, you're beautiful,
and not once did you do anything wrong.
So, whatever you do,
you must not make
a bad choice because of me.
Tell her that, will you?
Sure, but for now, let's run.
Father!
Mr. Seo I-deuk!
Kill her!
Min-ji!
A strange thing for a boy to have.
I made the plum blossoms bloom
in the garden with my own hands.
Grandma, no!
Mi-ju, please! No!
Mi-ju, no! This can't be!
This is the wrong order!
I said this bitch goes first!
- No!
- You psycho bitch!
Spit it out. Spit it out right now!
Open her up.
- Take the thread out!
- Please don't do that. Please!
Please!
No!
Sade.
Grandma.
Grandma?
Grandma, she…
Because of me, she…
You can't die, Grandma!
You can't just leave me!
As long as she's still breathing.
The lamp.
Where is the lamp?
You need to use your last wish on me.
This bitch has already stopped breathing.
Don't hold out too long,
or that bitch dies too.
But before that, we'll slice
this bitch open and take my thread out.
She swallowed my thread, you see.
No!
No! Don't!
Come on in!
Let's go!
Drag her down to the basement!
Let go of me!
Dr. Choi, get it together.
Help me take her.
You had the chance to kill me, so why?
Why didn't you kill me?
You still have a job to do.
You need to come and slit my throat.
Move aside.
Please, Brother.
End my son's life.
That is the reason I walked all night
to find and bind you.
I beg of you, my brother.
You fucking bastard, I'll kill you!
Call on Iblis!
Use your final wish
to transfer the lamp to me!
Make the wish for me!
I would rather make this decision
than transfer my wish.
You psycho bitch, do you want to die?
Kill me. Go on!
Yeah? Then I'll kill you myself.
I saw it.
A thousand years ago, when you were dying,
Iblis revealed the lamp himself
to save you.
Please use one of your wishes
to save this girl.
Please, I beg you!
It would be nice
for such a moment to come once more.
Come, Iblis!
Father!
Father.
No!
Father!
So the thing you longed for
was this war.
No.
The thing I longed for…
was victory.
Father?
Father!
I'll kill you!
Are you okay? Are you hurt at all?
Grandma was…
Grandma and Sade are…
The individual had no breath
or pulse upon rescue.
Clean with no visible trauma.
Let's contact the Jeil Hospital ER--
No.
Let's go straight to the funeral home.
She's dead.
I know that.
But legally, a doctor must pronounce
the death before any funeral arrangements.
- We need to confirm her identity.
- I know her.
And according to the law…
dentists can also pronounce someone dead.
Ms. Oh Pan-geum.
Time of death.
October 5th…
at 18:23.
She has passed.
I will now also give you sorrow
I will give you sorrow
More precious than love
Other genie, what does Oh Pan-geum
ask the most besides the weather?
Ms. Oh Pan-geum searched the following.
Ways to heal my dear Ka-young's illness.
How to fix a psychopath.
Foods that are good for psychopaths.
An old woman who had laid
A few tangerines on the street
KA-YOUNG, YOU'RE BEAUTIFUL TODAY AS ALWAYS
Shivering from a lifetime of cold
On a winter's night
FROM SORROW TO JOY
POETRY BY JEONG HO-SEUNG
To you, who rejoiced as you haggled
The price of tangerines
I shall show you sorrow's equal face
When I called out to you from the darkness
Please leave.
We will wash and dress the deceased.
Not once did you show me an equal smile
When a frozen corpse
Froze yet again under a straw sack
GRANDCHILD: KI KA-YOUNG
You did not so much
As cover it with another sack
For your indifferent love
For your tears
That seem incapable of flowing
It's uncomfortable.
I will now also give you waiting
Just put up with it for today.
You must.
Every decision I made
was for our happiness.
But because Grandma just died,
this is all so uncomfortable right now!
You're uncomfortable?
You feel uncomfortable
about making the wrong call?
What about me?
I lost Grandma, and…
Though it was only a short while, I…
So you tough it out too.
So if I decide something…
it makes everyone unhappy like this.
Be my friend.
What happens if I say I don't want to?
You and me, we're both negative ones.
You don't have a choice.
Multiply us, and we'll be at least one.
That's why we're friends.
I really am a negative one.
Your mom sent this
to cover the cost of the funeral.
I will put an end to the heavy snow
That once fell on this world
You said you were going
to a better place than Hawaii.
How could you come back to us like this?
Goodness me.
Goodness, what to do?
I will take the spring snow
That fell on the barley fields
And visit the sorrows of the people
Shivering with cold
I will walk the snowy paths with you
Where it no longer snows
Would you look at that?
She's like that
even at her grandma's funeral?
She sure is strange.
She hasn't shed a single tear.
Must you act strange on a day like this?
This is why I said
Gyeong-seok should hold her picture!
Mom.
Mom!
We will talk of the power of sorrow
And walk all the way
To the sorrow of waiting
Subtitle translation by: Jimin Choi